<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thrive on chrislindsay.org</title>
    <link>http://localhost:3000/tags/thrive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thrive on chrislindsay.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 19:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:3000/tags/thrive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Today, Not Someday</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/blog/todaynotsomeday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/blog/todaynotsomeday/</guid>
      <description>Hi, everyone, welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s live video. Thanks for joining me. Today I want to talk about a quote that I saw this week on a television show and it was called, &amp;ldquo;Today, not someday.&amp;rdquo; It got me thinking back to, well, why not today? Why many of us think including myself, think that dreaming of doing things someday, is actually more attractive than taking action today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valuing Challenge</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/blog/challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/blog/challenge/</guid>
      <description>Hello. Thanks for watching. My name is Chris Lindsay Thanks for taking the time to watch this live video.
I want to talk to you this week about what I believe is my most important core value.
This value is something that you might not even consider to be one that you&amp;rsquo;d want to hold. In fact, it might be one that you might want to consider avoiding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Agility</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/blog/emotional_agility/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/blog/emotional_agility/</guid>
      <description>Hi guys, welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s live video. Thanks for joining me. I want to talk today about stuff that I was writing about in my journal this morning. When you think about something which is important to you, something that you want to achieve, it can be anything really, it might be a new job, or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re planning to run a marathon, or give a presentation in front of maybe a hundred people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living in alignment with your values helps you Thrive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/blog/values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/blog/values/</guid>
      <description>And we&amp;rsquo;re live. Hello, thanks for joining me on today&amp;rsquo;s live video. Today I&amp;rsquo;m looking at an area which most people overlook when it comes to a thriving life. I know I did. I knew this area was important, but it&amp;rsquo;s one that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t considered, that if you ignored it could lead to stress. So keep watching to find out what it is.
Hi, my name is Chris Lindsay, and in recent videos I&amp;rsquo;ve been discussing key areas about how to reduce stress in your life, and get out of survival mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Willpower Doesn&#39;t Work and what you should instead.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/blog/willpower_doesnt_work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 19:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/blog/willpower_doesnt_work/</guid>
      <description>Hi, there! I think we&amp;rsquo;re live. Thank you for joining me again on today&amp;rsquo;s live video. Today, I want to talk about willpower and environment, and why one is better than the other, but keep watching to find out. Imagine a scenario where you&amp;rsquo;ve decided to give up sugar. You watched my video on nutrition and you know that sugary treats give you energy spikes followed by sugar crashes, which aren&amp;rsquo;t great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do this one thing to Thrive! Watch to find out.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/blog/exercise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/blog/exercise/</guid>
      <description>Life can be stressful. In fact, let&amp;rsquo;s be honest - life is full of stress. We have hectic lives with constant demands on our time and money pressures. The list goes on.
Stress triggers the release of chemicals into the body which set off a chain reaction. Necessary if you are facing a wild animal. No so much if you’re worried about bills you need to pay or ‘that’ meeting with your boss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prescribing Nature</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/blog/2019-01-20-nature/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/blog/2019-01-20-nature/</guid>
      <description>Hi. Thanks for joining me on today&amp;rsquo;s live video. My name is Chris Lindsay.
This is the third video in the series on how to get out of survival mode. Today I want to talk about prescribing yourself nature. I had a friend who shared with me an interesting post about doctors in Shetland prescribing nature to their patients. Instead of describing them a drug or pill, they were prescribed getting out into nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating to Thrive.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/blog/eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/blog/eating/</guid>
      <description>Hi, thanks for taking the time to watch this live video. This is the second video on the series of How to Get Out of Survival Mode and in this video, I discuss nutrition. My name is Chris Lindsay, thanks for watching.
Stress and eating. Stress can influence our food choices, so when you&amp;rsquo;re stressed out from whatever might be stressing you, your boss or colleagues, what foods do you crave?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep to Thrive!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/blog/sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/blog/sleep/</guid>
      <description>Hi. My name is Chris Lindsay, from Chrislindsay.org. Welcome to this live video. This is the first in a series of videos on helping you to get out of survival mode. What if there was one thing you could do that by spending more time doing each day, you&amp;rsquo;d help prevent type 2 diabetes and heart disease. You&amp;rsquo;d feel better physically and emotionally. You&amp;rsquo;d boost your immune system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>